muslimvideo.com 2016-06-28

# Muslim Video - upload Broadcast and share your free Islamic videos media - مسلم فيديو - الفيديو العربي -English and Arabic videos

This privacy policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect and receive. 

**\- General**  
We gather user information to provide you with a customized experience on our site. Your user information helps us tailor the content, services, goods and advertising to your current and future needs. For this reason, we may ask you to register or to provide personal information when you post comments, enter a contest, order products, subscribe to a newsletter and/or visit certain areas of our site. If you choose not to register you may not have access to areas that require personal identification. 

**\- Use of Information**  
When you register, we ask for your e-mail address, a unique nickname selected by you and other information. Once you are a registered user you can update your profile and may be able to provide additional preferential information.

All communication on the Internet takes place between pairs of IP Addresses. Our Web servers will log the IP address that any connection is made from. We may use these IP addresses to help diagnose technical problems or prevent abuse of our systems or other site users. Your IP address may also be used to gather aggregate demographic data and target advertisements accordingly.

Your browser has options to accept, reject, or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. A cookie is a small line of text that is stored with your Web browser for record-keeping purposes and to help us provide better service to you. We use cookies to save your password (in an encrypted format) on your machine so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and track your downloads from our site.

Our site contains links, including banner and other ads, to other Websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. Our site may also link to Websites that feature our trademarks and names along with trademarks and names of other companies. You should look at the privacy policy on that co-branded Website, as the co-branded Website may not be under our control.  
Applications you use or download from our site may contain third party digital rights management systems DRMS which may allow for communication between your software and the third party and utilize security features (e.g., preventing distribution of or access to the applications in the event of unauthorized use). These DRMS are subject to their own license agreements and you agree that we shall not be responsible for any loss or damage of any sort relating to the use of the DRMS or your dealings with such third parties. The applications may also contain DRMS produced by us which allow for communication between the applications you use or download and our systems and which collect information describing your computer system in order to prevent illegal or unauthorized use of the applications.

For reasons such as improving member experience and providing customized communications to our users, we may receive information about you from third party sources and our web logs and add it to the information that we have received from you. Web logs automatically record anything a web server sees, which may include e-mail addresses you enter into a form or pages viewed by a user at a particular IP address.

**\- Information Sharing**  
We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties, aside from entities that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders or processing payment, that either are bound to comply with our privacy policy or have privacy policies that protect your information unless you have opted-in to such sharing. If you have previously opted-in to such sharing under a prior privacy policy version, you are still considered to have opted-in under this privacy policy. As stated, and whether or not you have opted-in, we may use third parties to accept and process orders for merchandise and products, including software, and such third parties may get access to your personal information for the purposes of providing services or products to you on our behalf. In addition, if you opt-out, we may share that information with third parties who send e-mails on our behalf so that they do not e-mail you.

However, we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety.

We may request demographic information from you (for example, your age) from time to time. We will not share that information in a manner that identifies you as an individual with any other entity, unless we let you know that at the time of collection or we have your permission. When we share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only.

In the event that we acquired by another company, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party.

**Opt-Out**  
If you provide us with your e-mail address, and do not opt-out of receiving e-mail from us, we may e-mail you with information, including information about selected third parties. If you do not want to receive information from us, you may decline to receive it (or Opt-Out) either when you provide personal information to us or you may update your profile. You may also choose to Opt-Out from certain types of e-mail by following the unsubscribe instructions that appear on each newsletter. You may also contact us as provided below. Please note that there might be a brief delay between when you submit your request to opt-out and when it is processed and reflected in our systems; accordingly you might continue to receive e-mails from us for a few days after you unsubscribe. We maintain records of those users who opt-out of specific e-mail options so that we do not e-mail them with respect to those types of e-mails, and we may share this information with third parties who send e-mails on our behalf so that they do not e-mail you; this information may also be contained in web logs (see above).

**\- Other**  
We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a separate database. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. We will protect the transmission of credit card information through industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.

We may offer chat, user reviews, multi-player games, bulletin board, or other public functions and any posting by you is considered public information available to other users. Any posting is governed by our Terms of Use. You should take care to not use personal information in your screen name or other information that might be publicly available to other users.

If a user elects to use our site for informing a friend about our site or particular features or content, we ask them for the friend's name and e-mail address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit our site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail.

Your personal information is password-protected, and you should take appropriate measures to protect the secrecy of your password. **If you use a computer in a public place or share a computer with others, remember to sign out and close your browser window when you finish a session with us in order to prevent others from accessing your personal information.**

We maintain archives of our web logs, database, and other systems and information. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived after we delete the information from its active database (see above regarding web logs). We maintain archives for disaster recovery, legal and other non-marketing purposes.

**\- Profile**  
You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of your profile by notifying us when you change your address, title, phone number, or e-mail address. If at any time you wish to update your information or stop receiving communication from us, sign in and then select update your profile to change your preferences.

**\- Contact**  
Please address comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy to us as follows: You may send us an e-mail at info@MuslimVideo.com 

**\- DMCA Policy**

Muslimvideo.com is Link or embed content that was already uploaded to popular Online Video Hosting Sites Like Youtube.com / Google Video / vimeo.com.   
All video hosting users signed a contract with these sites when they set up their accounts which forces them not to upload illegal content.  
By clicking on any Links to videos while surfing on Muslimvideo.com you watch content hosted on third parties and Muslimvideo.com can not take the responsibility for any content hosted on other sites.  
We do not promote any illegal conduct of any kind. Links to the videos are submitted by users and managed by users.  
All youtube videos are the property of its respective owners, these videos are embeded by our users in Muslimvideo.com, The youTube TOS states the following - " You also hereby grant each user of the Service a non-exclusive license to access your Content through the Service, and to use, reproduce, distribute, display and perform such Content as permitted through the functionality of the Service and under these Terms of Service. ~~" [[youTube TOS part 6C]](http://www.youtube.com/t/terms)

**Copyright Notice as Required By U.S. Code Title XVII Chapter 5, Section 512**

_**Copyright Holders**_ :آ If you contend this site contains copyrighted material for which you are the copyright holder, please notify us using a DMCA compliant takedown notice us at: Muslim video (info @ muslimvideo.com )

**Notice and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement Pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.**

If you believe that you hold a claim of copyright infringement against us submit notice of your claim to the following Designated Agent:

  * Service Provider: **آ  _____________________**
  * Email Address to Which Notification Should Be Sent:آ  **___________________**
  * Physical Address: __________________
  * Fax Number: ________________

To be effective, the notification of your claim of copyright infringement should be written and should include the following:

  * A statement that you are the owner of the exclusive right you claim has been infringed, or a statement that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that has allegedly been infringed.
  * A statement, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notification is accurate.Your signature. (The signature may be electronic.)
  * The identification of the copyrighted work you claim has been infringed. (If you claim that multiple copyrighted works have been infringed you can submit one notification with a list of the allegedly infringed works.)
  * Identification of the material that you claim to be infringing and information reasonably sufficient to permit Forty Fit and Fabulous to locate the material.
  * Information reasonably sufficient to permit usآ to contact you, including your address, telephone number, fax number and, if available, an electronic mail address.آ  _You can provide contact information for the owner of the exclusive right that you claim has been infringed if you are not the owner, but rather authorized to act on behalf of the owner._
  * A statement you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.

We will respond to any DMCA complaints in a timely manner. Should you be the copyright holder of a specific piece of content featured on this site without your permission, weآ will remove it in a timely manner once notified.

_**Site Users**_ :آ All users of this site agree to be bound by our DMCA compliance policy and notice as a condition of using the site. آ You agree not to post copyrighted material for which you are not the copyright holder. If we receive notice that copyrighted material has been posted to the site by someone other than the authorized copyright holder, we will expeditiously remove the content and replace it with a notice that the content has been removed, or otherwise notify the poster that the content has been removed. آ Finally, all users are on notice that repeated posting of copyrighted material by a user will result in termination of their account or subscriber access.

**\- Binding Agreement**  
Your use of our site, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. By using our Site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the statement has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.
